SOTARO YOSHIMOTO

1 559 588 4242

Sotaro.yoshimoto@gmail.com

Results-oriented Web Developer and Blockchain Developer with considerable training and enterprise experience in Web site design and in coding, and testing of Web applications, and in the formation, planning, and implementation of online business ventures.

EXPERIENCE

JUL 2021 – CURRENT SOFTWARE ENGINEER, SOROC TECHNOLOGY

VAUGHAN, CA

Develop Blockchain Platform

- Built from scratch marketplace in NextJS in four months.
- Design and build patterns of chains and mainly developed Cross-Chain by Solidity, Rust & Web3.js
- Develop an analytics engine for the marketing team to help them understand the marketing ROI

OCT 2018 – MAY 2021 FULL STACK DEVELOPER, XTREAM

MILANO, ITALY

Developed XTREAM Company Website

- Ported the lonic Angular Sales funnel to React and GraphQL for rapid prototyping and split testing.
- Ported the deprecated native lonic library to Webpack 5 speeding up local and remote builds up to 6x.
- Developed a no-escape method that increases local development speed by a factor of 10 in your workflow
- Ensuring quality standards through regular code reviews of contractor's codebase contributions.

Developed Job Platform

- Developed a job market platform in Node.js with MongoDB and ReactJS.
- Created the "PAYMENT INTEGRATION" using Chargebee.
- Integrated Stripe API to make payments

NOV 2015 - SEP, 2018

FULL STACK DEVELOPER, GRUPPO RONCAGLIA

ROMA, ITALY

Develop Blockchain Platform

- Participated in pair programmed with 3 engineers, and reviewed team's code to provide additional perspective and catch previously missed errors.
- Worked with Quality Assurance to get new pages/products tested, and addressed any issues within 48 hours
- Designed and implemented web applications along with 3rd-party software integrations as a web team liaison for all inter-departmental and customer-facing projects.
- Cooperate with designers to create clean interfaces and simple, intuitive interactions and experiences.
- Developed E-commerce sites, Sports sites with Codeigniter, Zend and Spring Framework and React.
- Developed several websites using ReactJs, AngularJs, VueJS as a javascript framework

DEC 2014 - SEP, 2015

BACKEND DEVELOPER. JOHO TECHNOLOGY

TOKYO, JAPAN

- Developed the Database of 20 websites of all sorts of education, management of students, course, scores sand tests for using MySQL, PostgreSQL.
- Completed 25 backend projects successfully as well using PHP, Laravel, Coelginiter with Strong background in a variety of database platforms such as MySQL, MongoDB, PostgreSQL

SEP 2013 – AUG, 2014 SOFTWARE ENGINEER, PIKKLES

TOKYO, JAPAN

- Designed and developed Front-end GUI for 12 applications using HTML/CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript. jQuery and Ajax.
- Completed of training in UX and UI design implementation
- Collaborated with desingers, project managers and developers and communicated clearly by using Slack, Skype, Jira, Zoom meeting and google meeting.

EDUCATION

SEP 2009 - AUG 2013

BACHELOR'S DEGREE. THE UNIVERSITY OF TOKYO

COMPUTER AND INFORMATION SCIENCE AND SUPPORT SERVICES.

SKILLS

Web Development

- HTML/CSS/BootStrap
- JavaScript/TypeScript
- ReactJS + React Native (Material UI, NextJS[SSR])
- VueJS
- NodeJS / Express / NestJS
- PHP with OOP, Laravel, CodeIgniter

Blockchain

- Web3.JS, Ethereum, Solana
- ERC20, ERC777, ERC223, ERC721, ERC1155 Smart Contract Development
- Crypto Collectible Platforms and Non-Fungible Tokens
- Impermanent loss, governance tokens
- P2P/Pool Lending and Borrowing

PROJECTS

Job Platform

- Developed a job market platform in NodeJS with MongoDB and ReactJS
- Created the "Payment Integration" using Chargebee.
- Integrated Stripe API to make payments

https://www.legably.com/



Advertisement Website

I have a project in progress and the client wanted to finish It in urgent. I worked 50 hours a week and completed it in Time. My role was React Full-Stack web developer in this Time.

https://sellercrowd.com/



NFT MarketPlace

NFT Marketplace by Solidity, Web 3. Js and Next.JS. My role was Smart Contract developer as well as web Developer

https://nftcars.me/

